I think social media can motivate and encourage you to become better,
just like I said earlier.
You see a video and think, “Wow, they can do that. I can't. I'd love to be able to do that too.”
That can be a positive influence, but I'd make sure that
I don't take more risk than I normally would just for the sake of a video.
In general, I'd also say you shouldn't try to do too much too quickly. I mean,
in my case, I started when I was 20, so I never felt any pressure.
I always thought I still had plenty of time. I didn't need to rush anything.
Slow progression is safe progression,
and I think you should enjoy every step along the way. If you do
20 jumps in a two piece tracking suit just to move straight into a wingsuit,
you miss out on all the fun you could have had without a suit, or with a two piece,
or with a one piece tracking suit. It's all a lot of fun, and they're all
important skills that help make you a good wingsuit BASE jumper later on.
Take it slowly, experience everything, do lots of easy jumps, and choose the days
when you push yourself and approach your limits very carefully.
Because if you want to improve, you do have to push your limits from time to time.
You just have to do it safely, pick the right days, and not do it every
single day, because otherwise an accident will happen sooner or later, and that's something you want to avoid.